总有一天
Someday,
我们会拿到我们的大佬警探徽章
we're going to get our big boy detective badges
然后我们就不用
and then we won't have to do
再干这种傻乎乎的巡逻了
these ridiculous uniform details anymore.
-但是今天可不行  -没错
- But today is not that day. - No, it is not.
我要去哪儿给老大买馅饼
So where am I getting these pastries for the boss?
博伊特喜欢法拉拉的
Uh, Voight likes Ferrara's.
我个人喜欢斯卡福里的
I personally think that Scafuri's is better.
-是吗  -当然了
- Is that what you think? - Of course.
那就法拉拉吧
Ferrara's it is.
-那就法拉拉吧  -等一下  就一下
- Ferrara's it is. - Oh, wait. Just a sec.
在这里等一下  我马上回来
Wait right here. I'll be right back.
托马  你在这里干什么
Toma! Hey! What are you doing here?
我本来以为你今天不上班
I thought, uh, today was your day off.
他们派我加班巡视
I got offered the detail on overtime,
推不掉
couldn't pass it up.
-加薪加班也不算坏  -没错
- Yeah, a little time-and-a-half never hurt anybody. - Right.
你没事吧
You okay?
是啊  只是...
Yeah, yeah. Just--
只是有点宿醉不醒
just a little hungover, that's all.
昨晚睡太晚了
Stayed out too late.
-好吧  -金  我...
- Okay. - Kim, I, uh...
-金  -我只是想...
- Kim! - I just want--
走了
Come on! Let's go.
好  我马上就来
Yeah, j--I will be right there.
抱歉  我们得回指挥中心报到
Sorry. We have to check in with the command post.
听着  等你宿醉的劲儿过去了
Listen, when you get over that hangover,
你就打电话给我  咱们喝一杯
you call me and we get that drink, okay?
-听上去不错  -喝水
- Sounds good. - And water.
宿醉要喝很多水
Plenty of water for that hangover.
没问题
You got it.
那家伙是谁
Who's that guy?
我在分局见过他
Seen him around the district.
他叫弗兰克·托马  他去年毕业的时候
His name's Frank Toma. I was his FTO officer
我是他的培训警官
when he came out of the academy last year.
人很不错
Good guy.
我之前说的不是他
He's not the guy,
如果你是这个意思的话
if that's where you were going.
不是  不过既然你这么说了
I wasn't, but now that you mention it...
他叫马特·米勒
His name is Matt Miller.
等等  是那个律师吗
Wait, the prosecutor?
我想你要说的应该是"助理地检"
I believe you mean "Assistant US attorney."
真厉害
How fancy.
去年在法庭认识他的
Mm. Met him in court last year.
五点钟方向有一辆黑色面包车  没有车牌
Hey, we got a dark van with no plates, 5 o'clock.
好的
All right, well,
那条小巷是不允许车辆进出的
that alley's supposed to be closed to traffic.
先生们
Hey, yo, gentlemen!
金  你看到了吗
Kim, you seeing this?
走
Go.
-亚当  -混蛋
- Adam... - Son of a bitch. All right.
疏散这片区域  快走  我去联系凯文
Clear this area and go. I got Kev!
E5021号  呼叫指挥中心
5021 Eddy. 10-1, 10-1.
派拆弹部队来
Roll us a bomb squad.
有一辆车中可能有炸弹
We've a van with a possible explosive device.
弗兰克  我需要你赶紧
Frank, I need you to move
帮我疏散这些人
and help me get these people out of here.
-收到  -弗兰克  弗兰克
- Copy that. - Frank! Frank!
好的
Yeah.
快走  快走  大家快走
Move, move, move! Everybody go!
-快走  -小心点
- Move! - Careful!
快点  快走  快走
Now, go! Move, move, move!
原创翻译  双语字幕
最新连载海外影视剧下载
请登陆 www.YYeTs.com
仅供交流学习  禁止商用盈利
快  快点走
Let's go. Keep going!
快快快
Go, go, go, go, go!
翻译     小酸奶   风城章鱼X   不高兴童鞋
警察
Hey! Police!
站住  警察
Stop! Police!
翻译     小萝莉   H小欠   Lynn_宁   圈圈
校对     圈圈
时间轴     西查   大喷子
快去  这边交给我
Go! I got him!
后期     8T
芝加哥
警署
第五季
第二集
总监     圈圈
托马  是我  我是金
Toma, it's me. It's Kim.
你在哪里  还在这边吗
Where are you? You still here?
给我发个信息
You know, shoot me a text.
我只想确认你没事
I just want to make sure you're okay.
汉克·博伊特警长  情报组的
Sergeant Hank Voight, Intelligence.
我是负责的特殊探员  史蒂夫·伯恩斯
Special Agent in charge, Steve Burns.
现在什么情况
Hey, what do we know?
不清楚有没有二次爆炸装置
Negative on a secondary device.
两名平民受伤死亡
We got two civilians DOA.
二十多人受伤  不少人轻伤
Two dozen injured, some severely.
一名嫌犯正送往芝加哥医院
One suspect on the table at Chicago Med.
要不是你的人发现了  情况可能更严重
Could've been a lot worse, if not for your people.
炸弹做得非常精细
The bomb is reasonably sophisticated,
但现在网络上有那么多资源
but with all the Internet sites these days,
去五金店几次就能
you could probably build a bomb like this
在自家车库造出
in your garage after a couple of visits
这种炸弹
to a hardware store.
那这件事就算作恐怖袭击了
So we're calling this what it is? Terrorism?
我觉得是这样
Appears that way to me.
我觉得这背后不是乌萨马·本拉登
I don't think we're dealing with Osama bin Laden,
但是他们也不蠢
but they're not stupid, either.
他们把炸弹安放到
They got a bomb into a secure location
人流量大的安全区域
loaded with civilians.
好吧  有人声称为此事负责吗
All right. Anyone claim responsibility?
还没有
Not yet.
这通常说明事情还没结束
That usually means they're not finished.
等我们处理完现场  就可以在21分局调查了
Once we clear this scene, we can run leads out of the 21st.
很期待与你合作
Look forward to working with you.
去抓到这群混蛋吧
Let's get these bastards.
看来我不用去买馅饼了
I guess I get out of buying the pastries.
这种苦中作乐的精神才对
That's the silver lining I'm talking about.
-现在掌握什么情况  -这辆车
- Well, what do we have? - The van was reported stolen
上周在盖奇公园报失
from the Gage Park area last week.
他们把这辆车停在
And apparently, they parked this van
这里其中一个车库里
in one of these garages down there,
因为街角的交通摄像头
because the traffic camera on the corner
在爆炸发生前五分钟
picked it up coming down the alley
拍到这辆车驶入小巷
five minutes before the blast.
所以要么是他们刚好走运
So either they got real lucky,
要么是他们知道那个车库
or they knew that the garage
就在封锁区内
was inside the frozen zone.
什么  你是说他们内部有人
What, you mean they got someone on the inside
知道我们的行动计划
with access to our ops plan?
是的
Yeah.
被撞的袭击者名叫巴希尔·瓦提夫
Offender who got hit by the car is Bashir Wateef.
他25岁  有过几次被捕记录
He's 25. A few arrests on his rap,
但大多为小偷小摸
but mostly misdemeanor property crimes.
没有这种程度的大罪
Nothing close to this.
他住在盖奇公园
He lives in Gage Park,
就是这辆车被偷的地方附近
the same neighborhood the van was stolen from.
和厄普顿一起去医院
Listen, grab Upton, head over to Med.
问出几个名字
Get me some names.
其他人都去盖奇公园
All right, the rest of you head over to Gage Park.
打探打探  软硬皆施
Hit some wards, twist some arms,
找你们的线人谈谈
talk to your CIs.
肯定有人知道些什么
Somebody out there knows something.
那里有很多讲阿拉伯语的人  老大
There's a lot of Arabic speakers out that way, boss.
我们可能需要懂阿拉伯语的人
We could use someone who speaks the language.
托马  他刚才也在这里执勤
Toma. He was working the detail too.
他说得很流利
He's fluent.
几周前还帮我们讯问了一个叙利亚证人
Helped us out with a Syrian witness a few weeks ago.
很好  找到他  然后去查
Good find. Grab him up, then make the rounds.
也许从当地清真寺开始查更好
Probably makes sense to start with the local mosques.
-好的  -好
- Okay. - A'ight.
不管你打来多少次
No matter how many times you call,
答案不会变  他不在
answer is still the same. He's not here.
等他来了我一定让他给你打回去
I will absolutely have him call you when he gets in.
好  真是疯了
Yeah. This is a madhouse.
再提醒提醒我为什么不能退休
Remind me again why I shouldn't retire.
我们要请弗兰克·托马去盖奇公园协助搜查
We need to borrow Frank Toma for a canvas over in Gage Park.
完全可以  如果你找得到他
He's all yours, if you can find him.
我找他找了一刻钟了
I've been trying to get him for the last 15 minutes.
应急办也联系不上他
OEMC can't raise him.
要么是他的无线电坏了  要么没电了
Either his radio is off, or the battery's dead,
而他的手机直接转语音信箱了
and his phone just goes straight to voice mail.
他在现场协助过我处理情况
You know, he was at the detail with me.
他帮我引导平民
He helped me clear civilians,
但之后就再没看见他
but I didn't see him after that.
也许送进医院了
Could be lying in a hospital somewhere.
不  他穿着制服
No. He's in uniform.
送医的话会通知我们的
We would have been notified by now.
就在刚才我还给他的搭档丹尼·罗斯派活
I assigned his partner, Danny Rose, a little while ago.
他现在在奥兹公园值班呢
He's doing a foot post by Oz Park.
他也许知道些什么
He might have heard something.
好的  我们去一趟
Great. We'll run over.
我也再问问医院  以防万一
I'll check the hospitals again, just in case.
谢谢
Thank you.
抱歉  你们不能进去
Sorry. You can't go in there.
-现在不行  他太虚弱  -艾普尔
- Not yet. He's too... - April,
你也知道出什么事了
you heard what happened.
除非你想让医院急救室明天再挤满人
Unless you want these bays filled up again tomorrow,
你就得让我们和他谈谈
you need to let us talk to him.
他需要治疗
He needs to be treated.
他刚刚炸了一个街市节
He just blew up a damn street festival.
我明白  相信我
I get it, trust me.
但现在他只是个病人
But right now, he's a patient.
我们的工作和职责
Our job, our duty,
就是帮助他  现在请退后
is to help him. Now please, back off.
你  在这条路上巡逻
For you, maybe hem down this way.
你负责这个街区
You just go down this block.
保持警惕
Keep your eyes open.
罗斯  罗斯
Hey, Rose. Rose.
怎么了  我搭档还好吧
What's up? My partner okay?
我们正在找他
We're trying to find him.
觉得你可能会知道他去哪了
Thought you might be able to tell us something.
我一听说爆炸了
I've been blowing up his phone
我就一直在联系他  直接转去语音信箱了
since I heard about the attack. I go straight to voice mail.
你最后和他说话是什么时候
When's the last time you spoke with him?
昨晚在酒吧
Last night. The bar.
他有女朋友吗  能联系的人之类的
Does he have a girlfriend? Someone else he would call?
女朋友  没有
Girlfriend? No.
我觉得不会有
Don't think so.
他挺虔诚的  常常祈祷唱经之类的
He's pretty religious. Prays a lot, or chants,
或者别的他们在清真寺做的事
or whatever the hell they do, some mosque.
他也常常待在家里陪父母
Spends a lot of time at home, too, with his parents.
好吧  如果你有他的回音了  就联系我
Okay. Well, if you hear from him, call me.
直接找我
Directly.
没问题
Sure thing.
我们去找他父母谈谈吧
Let's try the parents.
您最后和您儿子说话是什么时候
When's the last time you talked to your son?
就今早他出门上班之前
This morning, before he left for work.
我们知道弗兰克要去街市节执勤
We knew Frank was working the festival,
而当我们看到爆炸的新闻之后
and when we saw the bombing on the news,
我们就想联系他问问安全
we tried calling to see if he was okay.
他是我们的独子
He's our only son.
如果他出了什么事
You know? If anything ever happened...
托马夫人  我们正在联系每家医院
Mrs. Toma, we are checking with all the hospitals
还有诊所  目前为止还没有发现
and the clinics--so far, nothing,
这是个好消息  所以别担心
which is good news, so try not to worry.
您介意我们去他房间看看吗
Do you mind if we have a look in his room?
检查下他的电脑什么的
Maybe check his computer?
你们觉得有帮助就行
If you think it might help.
-会有帮助的  -这边请
- It could. - Please.
这么大一场恐怖袭击
How does a cop just disappear
一个警察怎么可能就找不到了
in the middle of a terrorist attack?
我的天啊
Oh my god.
安东尼奥
Antonio...
这  这根本说不通
This--this doesn't make sense.
他在街市节  有炸弹炸了
He was at the festival, a bomb exploded,
之后再没人见过他
and no one has seen him since.
很不幸  我觉得非常说得通
Unfortunately, it makes perfect sense.
很遗憾
Sorry.
我不知道他为什么要看那种网站
I don't know what he was doing on that site,
但我觉得应该向你汇报
but I thought I should call you.
-还好你汇报了  -安东尼奥还在搜索
- Glad you did. - Antonio is still searching.
看着可不太妙
Certainly doesn't look good.
警长  这绝对不可能
Sarge, there's no way.
肯定会有别的解释的
There's got to be another explanation.
比如说  他只是好奇了
Like, maybe he was just being curious.
是啊  也没准他参与进去了
Yeah. Or maybe he was involved.
把我们的行动计划告诉袭击者了
Gave the bombers our ops plan.
更没准是袭击者研究了过去五年
Or maybe they watched every other event
我们做的每一次安保布置
we've held there for the last five years.
每次我们都是那一套
We do it the same way every time.
好吧  你喜欢这小子
Okay. You like the kid.
但你不能被情感遮蔽了  明白吗
You got to take the blinders off, understand?
我每天和他一辆巡逻车
I sat in a patrol car with him
巡逻八小时  足足一个月
for eight hours a day, for a month straight.
我跟你说  这人心啊
Look. You never really know
你是永远没法看透的
what's going on inside someone's head.
回去再和他父母谈谈
Go back in there, talk to the parents,
看还能有什么发现  但不要表露你的情绪
see what you can find out. But don't tip your hand.
鲁塞克  开始查吧
Ruzek, start digging.
就像我在电话里告诉你的
Okay, like I told you on the phone,
新人巡警弗兰克·托马  失踪了
rookie patrol officer Frank Toma--he's gone missing.
手机打不通  已经给他的车发通缉了
Phone's dead. Got a BOLO out on his car.
他最后一次出现是在街市节
The last time he was seen was at the festival.
托马在街市节执勤
Toma was working the festival
而你在他的上网记录里找到了恐怖分子网站
and you found jihadist websites on his browser?
毫不意外
Not surprised.
什么意思
What do you mean?
我们也在注意托马
Toma's been on our radar.
他这几个月每天晚上
He's been attending evening prayers
都要去马尔科姆清真寺做晚祷
for several months at the Malcolm Shabob mosque,
瓦提夫也去这个思想极端的清真寺
the same radical mosque that Wateef goes to.
这么说你们也在追查他
So you've been tracking him?
没有  只是有点疑心而已  直到现在
No, he was just a blip. Till now.
我们从这里接手吧
We'll take the lead from here.
等等  托马是我们的人
Wait a second. Toma's one of ours.
我们不会撤出的
We're not going anywhere.
有道理
Fair enough.
那么有消息就保持沟通吧
Let's agree to keep each other informed.
再见
Sir.
查得怎么样了
Okay, where are we?
你们去过马尔科姆清真寺吗
Have you ever been to the Malcolm Shabob mosque?
没有  我们的祈祷
No. We go to prayers
都是在这里的社区中心做的
right here at the community center.
那弗兰克呢
And what about Frank?
也不去  他和我们一起参加祷告
No. He comes to services with us.
你为什么要问这些
What are all these questions?
你们有没有发现他最近交了什么新朋友
Have you noticed any new friends recently?
也许是你们以前没见过的人
Maybe someone you haven't seen before?
你是在说弗兰克与这场袭击有关吗
Are you suggesting that Frank is involved in the attack?
-太可笑了  -不是
- That's ridiculous. - No.
不是  我只是在问
No. There's just certain questions
我必须要问的问题
that I need to ask.
这只是走个过场
It's just standard police procedure.
他们要么是奥斯卡获奖演员
Well, either they are academy Award-winning actors,
要么就是真的什么也不知道
or they don't know a damn thing.
我觉得我们是想太多了
Look, I-I think we're letting our imaginations run wild.
你觉得这孩子像是个恐怖分子吗
I mean, does this look like a terrorist to you?
安东尼奥
Antonio.
来看看这个
Come check this out.
好
Okay.
这些是...情书
So they're... love letters?
卡片
Cards.
我猜是这个人写给他的
I'm guessing from him.
这个人是布莱恩·穆尼
Oh. That's Brian Mooney.
在我们辖区巡逻
He works patrol at our district.
我都不知道这回事
I had no idea.
我们去找这个人
Let's find this guy.
你最好好好听我说话
You best listen to me now.
我们没有那么多时间  瓦提夫先生
We don't have a lot of time, Mr. Wateef.
我们需要参与这场爆炸案的
We need to know the names of the people
所有人的名字
involved in the bombing.
我们要知道他们现在的位置
We need to know where they are
以及他们的其他计划
and what else they have planned.
我什么都不知道怎么告诉你
I can't tell you what I don't know.
你应该是还不明白你做了些什么
I don't think you understand what you did.
上百名群众丧了命
Hundreds of people are dead.
妇女  儿童  警官
Women. Children. Police officers.
我们是到了车库
I didn't know about the bomb
我才知道有炸弹的  我发誓
until we got to the garage, I swear.
这不重要
That doesn't matter!
现在你就是这座城市有史以来
Right now, you are the face of the biggest mass murder
最大屠杀事件的代名词
in the history of this city.
你认识弗兰克多久了
How long have you known Frank?
这人是扎韦恩  他是警察
That's Jawean. He's a cop?
他姓什么
What's Jawean's last name?
不知道
Don't know.
我是几个月前在清真寺认识的他
Met him a few months ago at the mosque.
他人很好  很爱说话
He's nice. Likes to talk.
他都说什么
About what?
-不知道  乱七八糟的  -比如
- I don't know. Stuff. - What, like
"我想帮你们炸烂一个街道庆典
"I want to help you blow up a street festival
谋杀无辜群众"那种话
and kill innocent people" type stuff?
-不是  -所以他没有参与这起案件
- No. - So he wasn't a part of this?
我不知道  他没告诉我
I don't know. He doesn't tell me
-还有谁也参与了  -"他"是谁
- who else is involved. - Who's "he?"
和你一起在面包车的那个人
The other guy in the van with you?
我不能说
I can't.
你显然认识和你一起在面包里的那个人
You obviously know the other guy in the van.
他叫什么名字
So what is his name?
What's his name?
这样吧  打电话联系联调局  让他们过来
You know what? Call the FBI. Get them down here.
他叫阿祖尔
His name is Azul.
阿祖尔什么
Azul what?
这个人是阿祖尔·拉希姆
All right. This is Azul Rahim.
他就是之前跑掉的那个人
This is the guy that got away.
马尔科姆清真寺
曾因伤人和抢劫入过狱
He's done time for assault and for robbery.
这位是他的妻子娜迪亚  最近的住所
This is his wife, Nadia. Their last known address
现为阿彻高地的一处空房
is now a vacant apartment in Archer Heights.
瓦提夫去年在一家清真寺认识了阿祖尔
Wateef met Azul at a mosque last year
在社交媒体上招募了他
when he recruited him on social media.
他说他在整起事件中
So he says his only involvement
唯一做的事就是为阿祖尔提供保护
in all of this was to provide security for Azul
并把面包车从车库开到庆典上
and to drive the van from the garage to the festival.
好的  那他是怎么说托马的
Okay. What does he say about Toma?
他把托马叫作"扎韦恩"
He recognized Toma as "Jawean."
-"扎韦恩"  -对
- "Jawean"? - Yeah.
他说他不知道他是否参与了爆炸案
He said he's not sure if he's connected with the bombing.
托马为什么要用化名
Why would Toma use an alias?
也许这是他的恐怖分子名
Well, maybe it was his terrorist name.
瓦提夫证实了托马也认识阿祖尔和他的妻子
Wateef confirmed that Toma also knows Azul and his wife.
不过警长  我们可能查到了阿祖尔的位置
But, Sarge, we might have a location on Azul.
我找到了一辆车
I found a car.
注册在了娜迪亚的名下  登记的是一处老地址
It's registered to Nadia under her name under an old address.
车牌查询系统七次将其标记在了盖奇公园附近
NVLS has tagged it seven times in the Gage Park area.
同时还有一位邻居指认这对夫妻
Also, a neighbor has placed the couple
住在梅普尔伍德的一间小公寓里
in a small apartment on Maplewood.
我刚拿到了搜查令
I got a hot and ready warrant
巡警已经准备就绪
and we got patrols sitting on it right now.
那好  我们行动
All right. Let's hit it.
大家都把眼睛睁大
All right, keep your eyes peeled.
我们要盲闯了
We're going in blind.
-准备好了吗  -好了
- You ready? - Yeah.
警察  不要动  女士
Police! Don't move, ma'am.
放下  放下
Drop it. Drop it!
把锤子放下
Drop the hammer!
好
Okay.
放下  把锤子放下
Drop it! Drop the hammer!
男性嫌犯从后门逃跑了
Male offender fleeing around the back.
快点放下
Do it now!
放下  放下
Drop it. Drop it!
好的  好的
Okay. Okay.
-最后一次  放下锤子  -拜托...
- Last time! Drop the hammer. - Please...
不要开枪
Don't shoot.
把它放下
Put it down!
不要...
Don't--
转过去
Turn over.
听着  你和霍斯特德一起进去
All right, listen. I want you to sit in with Halstead,
看看能从他嘴里挖出什么来
see what you can get out of this guy
趁国土安全部还没来把他带走
before DHS comes to scoop him up.
收到
Copy.
-你快点查查这些电脑和手机  -这就办
- Hey, get into those laptops and phones, you hear? - I’m on it.
找到托马了吗
Any word on Toma?
没  我们正在想办法追踪他的男朋友
No. Um, we're trying to track down his boyfriend.
他是个警察  名叫穆尼
He's a cop named Mooney.
那这个人在哪里
Okay. Where the hell is he?
他在纽约  看望他的母亲
He's in New York, visiting his mom.
他不接电话  但我们已经把他盯住了
He's not answering his phone, but we're all over him.
我们给他的母亲和妹妹打了电话
We have calls into his mother and sister.
好的
A'ight.
跟我们说说扎韦恩吧
Tell us about Jawean.
他在这起案件中起到了什么作用
What's his part in all this?
扎韦恩有没有帮助你们
Did Jawean help you in any way?
告诉我们他在哪里
Tell us where he is
你自己也可以好过点
and make things easier for yourself.
我没什么好说的
I got nothing to say.
我要找我的律师
I want my lawyer.
我还要和我的妻子说话
And I want to speak to my wife.
我们在这里干什么  汉克
What are we doing here, Hank?
可能马上又会发生另一场袭击
There might be another attack coming soon.
我们还没抓到托马
Toma is still out there.
却在和这个以为自己是英格兰国王的男人聊天
We're talking to this guy like he's the king of England.
你有时间吗  海莉
You got a sec, Hailey?
-嗨  -怎么了
- Hey. - What's up?
老埃和我要来接手了
Al and I are going to step in.
把阿祖尔带去审问
Take Azul on a little bathroom break.
-我们才开始  -没时间了
- We're just getting started. - We don't have time.
他还不知道老婆死了
He doesn't know his wife is dead.
杰和我可以利用这点
Jay and I can use that.
我明白
Guys, I get it.
我也想痛揍他一顿
I want to beat his ass too.
但我们不能随意那么做
But we don't get carte blanche for that kind of thing.
我们会拿到你们要的信息  再给我们点时间
We'll get what you want. Just give us more time.
-就5分钟  -行
- Five minutes. - Great.
就5分钟
Five minutes.
她很美
She's beautiful.
警探把她从学校里接出来了
Detectives picked her up from school.
她平安无事
She's safe and sound.
正在来这里的路上
On her way here right now.
你老婆在另一个房间里等着
Your wife is in another room, waiting.
这句话很甜蜜
It's a sweet note.
没有什么能取代我心中你的位置
"Nothing will ever take your place in my heart."
但你是认真的吗
But did you mean it?
还是说圣战的破事比你女儿更重要
Or is this jihad crap more important than your little girl?
你会烂在监狱里一辈子
You're going to prison forever.
没其他可能
There's no way around that.
但你还能为娜迪亚和你女儿做对的事
But you can still do right by Nadia, by your daughter.
如果你合作
If you cooperate,
我们会帮你  给她们一条活路
we will help you. Give them a life.
-娜迪亚和此事无关  -是吗
- Nadia isn't involved. - Really?
那堆砸碎的电子设备让我不这么认为
I got a pile of smashed-up electronics that say otherwise.
联邦探员如果查得够深
You know if the Feds dig deep enough,
会发现更多
they're going to find something else.
那你的女儿会怎样
And then what happens to your little girl?
去寄养中心吗
Foster care?
或者我们把她遣送回叙利亚
Or maybe we ship her back to Syria,
去难民营  你希望这样吗
to a refugee camp? You want that?
她不该受到这种待遇
She didn't ask for any of this.
我要先和我老婆说话
I want to speak to my wife first.
在你供出信息之后
After you give us something.
我要白纸黑字的协议
I want this in writing.
没问题
No problem.
首先  我们需要信息
First, we need information.
穆克什·哈桑
Mukesh Hassan.
那是谁
Who's that?
他制造了炸弹  放在车里
He made the bomb. Put it in the van.
怎么才能找到他
How do we find him?
不用  他会找到你们
You don't. He finds you.
说明白点
Do better than that.
马上还有一场袭击
There's another attack coming.
他们在我车里放炸弹的时候
When they put the bomb in my van,
就计划着第二场爆炸  我看到了
there was a second bomb. I saw it.
哪里  目标是什么
Where? What's the target?
没了  我说完了
No. No more. I'm done.
我需要律师
I want a lawyer.
我要书面协议  我现在要见我老婆
I want the deal in writing, and I want to see my wife, now.
派对到此结束
Party's over.
国土安全局带着文件来了
Homeland Security is here with paper.
你想见你老婆吗
You want to see your wife?
看看吧
There you go.
别难过
Don't be sad.
她为你们的事业而死
She died for the cause.
穆克什·哈桑
Mukesh Hassan.
Mukesh Hassan?
他地位很高
He's high up the ladder.
他为欧洲那几起大规模袭击事件负责
He's responsible for several major attacks in Europe.
我只是转述他告诉我的
I'm just telling you what he told me.
我告诉你
And I'm telling you,
哈桑和阿祖尔合作的概率是千分之一
the odds of Hassan working with Azul are 1,000 to 1.
那我下注了
Yeah, I'd take that bet.
-什么  -鉴证科刚反馈回了
- Excuse me? - Forensics just got back
炸弹上的指纹
with the prints off the bomb.
定时装置上有一小块指纹
A small piece of the timing mechanism,
和穆克什·哈桑的指纹一致
and it's a match for Mukesh Hassan.
来看看穆克什·哈桑
Meet Mukesh Hassan.
他是伊拉克民族主义者
He's an Iraqi nationalist.
恐袭爆炸装置解析中心数据库里录有他的指纹
Fingerprints showed up in the TEDAC database.
-恐袭爆炸装置解析中心  -一弗吉尼亚的研究室
- TEDAC? - It's a lab, in Virginia.
所有从中东收回的简易爆炸装置
All IEDs recovered from the Middle East
都被送去那里处理以提取指纹和DNA
are sent there to be processed for fingerprints and DNA.
那我们还知道关于他的什么
So what else do we know about him?
他是伊斯兰国的拥护者
He's an ISIS sympathizer.
是所有人的密切关注对象
Uh, he's on everybody's watch list.
国土安全局现在宣称
Homeland Security is now saying
有未经证实的消息说
that there are unconfirmed reports
他于4月通过南部边境进入美国
that he entered the US over the southern border in April.
我听着挺可信的
Sounds pretty confirmed to me.
是啊  欢迎来到芝加哥
Yeah. Welcome to Chicago.
他没去看小熊队比赛
Instead of catching a Cubs game,
而是和阿祖尔还有瓦提夫成立了一个恐怖组织
he sets up a terrorist cell with Azul and Wateef,
招募了一个完美的本土拥护者
and they recruit the perfect homegrown sympathizer.
一个穆斯林警察  弗兰克·托马
A Muslim cop, Frank Toma.
他们的内线
Their inside man?
托马有新线索吗
So any new leads on Toma?
巡逻队拿到他的照片了
They got his face out to patrol
城里的交通机构也拿到了
and every city transportation agency,
但目前为止  半个影子都没有
but right now, he's a ghost.
他男朋友那儿有进展吗  穆尼
Well, any updates on his boyfriend? Uh, Mooney?
他在回芝加哥的路上
Yeah. He's on his way back to Chicago.
20分钟后到达奥黑尔国际机场
Lands at O'Hare in 20 minutes.
确定他到家时  你们在那儿等他
Make sure you're waiting for him when he gets home.
布莱恩
Brian.
-金  -一路顺利吗
- Kim. - How you doing?
我是安东尼奥·道森  我们是来说...
Antonio Dawson. We're here to talk--
我知道你们来的原因
I know why you're here.
很好  他在哪里
Okay, good. Where is he?
我不知道
I don't know.
我希望我知道  但是...
I wish I did, but...
当我听说爆炸事件时
When I heard about the bombing,
我知道他在节日现场工作
I knew he was working the festival.
所以我试着打给他  但是转到语音信箱了
So I tried calling him, but it went to voice mail.
我打给警局  但那儿乱套了
I called the district, but it was crazy.
他们什么也不能告诉我  所以我飞回来了
They couldn't tell me anything. So I flew right back.
我降落后  语音信箱里有弗兰克的留言
When I landed, I had a voice mail from Frank.
他说了什么
What'd he say?
这说不通
Didn't make sense.
他很难过
He was upset.
说自己犯了个错
Rambling about making a mistake.
一直说自己搞砸了
Kept saying he screwed up,
说本可以阻止爆炸
that he could've prevented the bombing.
说恨透了自己  都是他的错
That he hates himself, that it's his fault.
他一直在这么说
Look, he was rambling.
这不合理
It wasn't rational.
能想到其他他可能消失的理由吗
Can you think of any other reason that he would disappear?
他最近真的很沮丧
He's been really depressed lately.
他和搭档相处得不太好
He's had a rough time with his partner,
丹尼·罗斯
Danny Rose.
那人的父亲是罗斯局长
His dad is Commander Rose.
我知道那是谁  这有什么问题
Yeah, I know who he is. What kind of problem?
开始只是新人被欺负的小事
At first, it was just rookie hazing.
但当丹尼发现弗兰克是穆斯林后
But when Danny found out Frank was Muslim,
事态就升级了
he went next level.
在他的更衣柜里涂脏兮兮的培根油脂
Smeared bacon grease on his locker.
挂上种族主义讽刺卡通画
Hung up racist cartoons.
然后几周前  他发现他是同性恋
Then a few weeks ago, he found out he was gay.
情况就更糟了
Things got worse.
怎么说
How so?
开始动手了
It started getting physical.
弗兰克吓坏了
Frank started freaking out.
他有没有在留言里说别的
On the voice mail, did he say anything else?
比如他在哪儿  或者他要去哪儿
Like, where he was, or where he was going?
没有
No.
他的声音很悲伤
He sounded sad.
迷茫
Confused.
他好像在说"再见"
Like he was saying "good-bye."
好  谢谢  金  继续找
All right. Thanks, Kim. Keep looking.
你准备什么时候告诉我弗兰克·托马的事
When were you going to tell me about Frank Toma?
我们还没有查清楚来龙去脉
We still don't have all the facts.
警监想让我们把这件事透明
The superintendent wants us out in front of this,
部门内发生的其它所有事都是
and every other damn thing that happens in this department.
我知道你现在很难理解
Now, I know you find it hard to comprehend,
但办案透明化是真的
but this transparency thing is real.
什么意思
Meaning what?
他们想让我跟媒体说
They want me to make a statement to the press
托马跟爆炸有关
about Toma's involvement in the bombing.
我们还不确定怎么会有关  甚至有没有关
We're still not sure how, or even if, he's involved.
现在  他只是擅离职守
Right now, he's just AWOL.
我来说几点
Let me connect a few dots.
他当时在现场
He was there at the scene.
爆炸发生后他就擅离职守
He's been AWOL since the explosion.
我们发现他跟已知的恐怖组织
We've connected him to known terrorist groups
和圣战网页有关联  有没有漏掉什么
and jihad websites. I miss anything?
我只是想照顾一下自己人
I'm just looking out for one of our own.
记得你以前也会这么干吗
Remember when you used to do that?
丹尼  你把他的照片发出去
Denny, you put his face out there,
他可能会藏得更深
you could drive him even further underground.
也许可以预防下一场袭击
Or we could prevent another attack.
老大  我有话跟你说
Hey, boss. I need a word.
等一下
Give me a minute.
不用等了  我们说完了
You don't need another minute. We're done here.
我这就发出去  汉克
I'm putting it out, Hank.
十分钟前我们
we got a hit on Toma's car
在河滨找到了托马的车
down by the river promenade about ten minutes ago.
好的  走吧
All right. Let's go.
车牌没错  是托马的车
Plates match. That's Toma's car.
弗兰克  你在里面吗
Frank, are you in there?
弗兰克
Frank?
我是金  你在里面吗
It's Kim. You in there?
安全
Uh, it's clear.
好  分开搜索  找到那孩子
All right, let's fan out and find this kid.
-好的  -走吧
- All right. - Come on. Let's go.
这边
This way.
小心  各位  老大刚刚打电话过来
Heads up, guys. Boss just called.
联调局探员来了  全副武装
Feds are on their way. They're rolling in heavy.
还是没有发现托马
Still no sign of Toma.
厄普顿和我去搜北边到公园边缘
Upton and I will cover the north end of the park.
收到
Copy.
去左边
Go left.
弗兰克  弗兰克  你在吗
Frank. Frank, are you out here?
弗兰克
Frank?
Frank.
是我  是
It's me. It's...
金
Kim.
放下枪  弗兰克
Put that gun down, Frank.
不行  我不能放下
I can't. I can't do that.
弗兰克  大家都在担心你
Frank, everybody's worried about you.
不管发生了什么事
Whatever it is that happened,
不管跟你有没有关系
whatever it is you're involved in,
-我们都能解决  -不是你想的那样
- we can fix it. - It's not what you think.
好吧  那你告诉我怎么回事
Okay, then just tell me what it is,
但你能放下枪吗
but can you put the gun down?
好吗  然后我们谈谈
Okay? So we can talk?
放下枪
Just put it down.
现在  现在都不重要了
It--it doesn't matter anymore.
那些人都死了
Those people are dead.
他们死了  什么都搞砸了
They're dead. Everything got messed up.
弗兰克  是我  好吗  你可以相信我
Frank, it's me. Okay? You can trust me, okay?
所有人都会说我是恐怖分子
Everyone is going to call me a terrorist.
你了解我  我不是恐怖分子
You know me. I'm not a terrorist.
我相信你  你不是恐怖分子
I believe you. You're not a terrorist.
我本想
I wanted--
我试过阻止这事
I was trying to stop this.
我  我应该
I--I should've--
我应该知道会这样
I should've seen it coming.
会怎样
Seen what?
我一直在等  等太久了
I waited. I waited too long.
这是我的错
It's my fault.
你冷静一点  好吗
I just want you to calm down, okay?
解释给我听
Help me understand.
我们觉得还有一场袭击
We think there's another attack coming.
你知道吗
Do you know anything about that?
弗兰克
Frank.
我的背包里
In my backpack.
有一个信封
There is an envelope.
它能解释所有的事
The envelope will explain everything.
信封里是什么  弗兰克  能解释什么
But what's in the envelope, Frank? What will it explain?
解释我做过的事  解释我想做的事
Everything I did. Everything I wanted to be.
弗兰克  天啊
Frank, for God's sake,
放下枪  联调局的人就要来了
put the gun down. The feds are coming.
弗兰克
Frank?
我希望你去告诉我爸妈
I want you to be the one to tell my mom and dad
发生了什么事
what happened.
我们一起说
We'll do that together.
我们一起解释
We'll explain together.
谢谢你一直对我这么好
Thank you for always being kind to me.
弗兰克
Frank!
金
Kim!
我知道这看上去很明显
Look, I know what it looks like,
但这解释不通啊
but it still doesn't make any sense,
因为他冲到现场
because he ran into the action,
跑向面包车  为了救更多的人
towards the van, to save more lives.
一直在现场  如果他是哈桑的内应
Keeping up appearances. If he's Hassan's mole,
那他获取情报的任务就完成了
then his part in getting the ops plan was done.
不对  在他自杀之前我看着他的眼睛
No. 'Cause I saw into his eyes before he killed himself.
他说他试过阻止他们
He said he was trying to stop them.
他没有理由骗我  而且他说他的背包里
He had no reason to lie to me, and he said he had an envelope
-有一个信封  -他在耍你
- in his backpack-- - He was playing you.
他都准备结束自己的生命了
He was about to take his own life.
为什么还要耍我
Why the hell would he play me?
他在拖延时间
He was stalling.
也许在考虑杀你
Probably thinking about killing you,
然后决定选择最简单的方式
and then decided to take the easy way out.
这就是他们在匡提科的侧写课上教你的东西吗
Is that what they teach you in your profiling class at Quantico?
金  金  够了
Kim. Kim. That's enough.
你有没有看过真正的凶手的眼睛
How you ever looked a real killer in the eye?
-带她走  -你知道它们是什么样的吗
- Get her out of here. - Do you even know what that looks like?
你要让我走开吗  真的吗
Are you benching me? Seriously?
-我们去走走  -你他妈凭什么让我走开
- Come on, let's take a walk. - What the hell are you benching me for?
不不不  别说了  继续走
No, no, no, don't say it. Just keep walking.
我让计算机实验室分析了
I had RCFL mirror the hard drive
托马背包里的笔记本硬盘
from the laptop we found in Toma's backpack.
他们发现了黑网上
They found all these IP addresses
所有激进的圣战网站的IP地址
from radical jihad websites on the dark web.
看来
It looks like
托马肯定在用化名扎韦恩·埃尔阿赛德
Toma was definitely using the alias Jawean Al'asad
上一些社交媒体
on some social media accounts.
所以扎韦恩和哈桑
Yeah, so Jawean and Hassan
一定是在干同一件事
were definitely rolling around in the same sandbox.
对  但这些都被加密了
Yeah, but these are all really well-encrypted.
解密信息
所以没有密码的话
So without the passwords,
技术部门也很难进入
even the tech guys are having a tough time getting in.
得费些时间
That's gonna take some time.
一定还有些什么
There's gotta be something else.
伯吉斯说背包里还有个信封
Hey, Burgess said there was an envelope in the backpack.
没看到
Oh, didn't see one.
金  这真的不是一个好主意
Kim, this is a bad idea on so many levels.
我们应该告知博伊特我们在做什么
We should let Voight know what we're doing.
如果我们找到什么的话会告诉他的
We'll let him know if we find something.
如果这是个陷阱呢  如果这是个诱杀陷阱呢
What if this is a set-up? What if it's booby-trapped?
如果哈桑和他的人在里面呢
What if Hassan and his guys are inside?
托马让我来这是有原因的
Toma sent me here for a reason,
不是为了杀我  我相信他
and it wasn't to kill me. I trust him.
你没有了解他到相信他的地步
You didn't know him well enough to trust him.
也许他就是为了这个才当警察的
He may have become a cop just for this.
这就是这些人做的事
That's what these people do.
"这些人"
"These people"?
恐怖分子
Terrorists.
他有故事要讲  安东尼奥
He had a story to tell, Antonio,
但他觉得没人会相信他
but he didn't think anyone would believe him.
所以我要去那个公寓
So I'm going into that apartment
补全他剩余的故事
to get the rest of that story.
如果你相信我的直觉  跟我来
If you trust my instincts, come.
如果不相信  待在这  决定权在你
If you don't, stay here. It's your call.
金...
Kim...
准备好了吗
Ready?
好了
Yeah.
好
Okay.
天啊  这都是什么
Oh my god. What the hell's all this?
你还相信他
You still trust him?
安东尼奥  看这个
Antonio, check this out.
是本日记
It's a journal.
有监视的照片  日期  时间
with surveillance photos, dates, times.
汽车炸弹
听我说
Okay, hear me out.
托马是在进行他自己的小卧底行动
Toma's running his own little undercover operation.
这是他卧底用的公寓
This is his cover apartment. Look.
这有情报部门  联调局  联合反恐工作小组的号码
Look, there's numbers for Intelligence, FBI, JTTF.
他为什么有这些部门的号码
Why else would he have that?
好吧  这可以解释他的化名问题
Okay. That might explain the alias.
对  他在调查那个清真寺
Exactly. Look, he's working the mosque.
在调查伊斯兰圣战组织  为了打入内部
He's working the jihad sites to--to get an in,
为了立案
to build a case.
他是想阻止他们
He was trying to stop them.
我们打给博伊特吧
Let's call Voigt.
是伯吉斯  你们他妈去哪了
It's Burgess. Where the hell are you?
我稍后会解释这一切的
I'll explain everything later.
打开免提  我得告诉所有人
Put me on speaker. Everyone needs to hear this.
好了  打开免提了
Okay, we're listening.
好  我们在奥克朗的一间公寓
Okay, we're in an apartment in Oak Lawn
就是托马用来进行对哈桑的小队
that Toma was using to run a solo undercover operation
进行单独卧底行动的公寓
on Hassan's crew.
汉克  他在监视这些家伙
Hank, he was doing surveillance on these guys.
我们有见面的日期  时间和地点
We have dates, times, locations of meetings,
不同参与者的照片
photos of different players,
车牌号码
license plate numbers.
两位  我在找进入
Guys. I'm looking for a password
托马的社交媒体账户的密码
to access Toma's social media accounts.
你们在日记里有看到什么能当做密码的吗
Do you see anything like that in the journal?
有可能有
Yeah, maybe.
安东尼奥现在正发给你
Antonio's sending it to you now.
好了  我收到了
All right, I got it.
密码错误
好了  我进去了
All right. I'm in.
那是节日上的面包车
That's the van from the festival.
托马看到这些家伙了
Toma had these guys in his sights.
他只是还不知道
He just didn't know it yet.
那是他所说的
That's what he was talking about.
他因为节日上那些人的死而怪自己
He blamed himself for the deaths of the people at the festival.
怎么了
Hey, what's going on?
我们找到了三天前
We found some photos taken three days ago
老昆西咖啡仓库的照片
at the old Quincy's Coffee Warehouse.
所有的参与者都在那
All of our players are there,
还有两辆车  其中一辆在节日炸弹事件中使用过
plus two vans, one of them used in the festival bombing.
我现在把照片发过去
I'll send a picture now.
那就是说外面还有一辆面包上面有炸弹
That means there's another van out there with a bomb in it.
拿到仓库的地址了
I got the address of the warehouse.
恩格勒路255号
255 Engler Road.
好了  大伙儿都准备好
All right, everybody, gear up.
鲁塞克  阿特沃特  你们俩在这里负责调查
Ruzek, Atwater, you stay here and run point.
挖一挖那些文件
Dig into those files.
看看下一个目标是什么
Figure out what the next target is.
收到
Copy that.
别说话  要不你就死定了
Don't say a word, or you die.
双手抱头
Hands on your head.
准备好了吗  行动
Ready? Go.
另一辆面包车在哪
Where's the other van?
下一个目标是什么
What's the next target?
太晚了  已经在发生了
You're too late. It's already happening.
今天结束之前  你就会埋葬很多你们的兄弟
Before the day is out, you will be burying many of your own.
你再说一遍
Say that one more time.
博伊特  博伊特警长
Voight! Sergeant Voigt...
说啊
Say it!
汉克  汉克
Hank, Hank.
汉克  汉克  汉克
Hank, Hank, Hank.
不要这样  兄弟
Not like this, man.
不要这样
Not like this.
好了  对那辆车发出注意警报
A'ight, put a BOLO out on that van.
然后联系州警察
Then contact state police.
我们需要能用到的所有人员
We need all available eyes we can get.
警长  一个附近的工人说
Sarge, a worker a few doors down
他看到两个中东男子
says he saw two Middle Eastern males
在我们来之前十分钟开走了一辆蓝色面包车
take off in a blue van ten minutes before we got here.
好  等一下  鲁塞克  你那有什么消息
All right. Hold on a sec. Ruzek, what do you got?
我们进了聊天室
We're in a chat room.
这里都在聊
There's all kinds of chatter
今天警察学院毕业典礼的事
about the police academy graduation today.
在海军码头
It's at Navy Pier.
好  通知巡警
All right, put that out to patrol right away.
各个方向都设置路障
And set up roadblocks in every direction.
收到
Copy that.
毕业典礼是什么时候
Hey, what time is the graduation?
还有两小时  警长
two hours, Sarge.
有问题
Something's wrong.
你听到哈桑说的了
You heard Hassan.
他说今天我们要埋葬自己人
He said we'd be burying our own today.
他们那种人不会透露线索的
Guy like that doesn't just hand out clues.
他和他的朋友都谈论一件事是有原因的
He and his friends are chatting up a storm for a reason.
他们在误导我们
They're pointing us in the wrong direction.
金  你到了吗
Kim, are you there?
怎么了  警长  我们刚走
What's up, Sergeant? We just left.
我们在去码头的路上
We're on our way to the pier.
好  查一下托马的日记
All right, look in Toma's journal.
看看有没有别的可能的目标
See if there are any other possible targets.
会面地点
我看看
Let me see.
看到一些咖啡厅
Got some coffee shops.
餐厅
Restaurants...
几个清真寺的名字
The names of a couple mosques.
等等
Wait.
我看到阿祖尔和哈桑的两个人在
We've got Azul and two of Hassan's guys in the stands of,
史密斯维尔高中体育馆看台上
Smithville High School stadium.
-有可能是那里  -对
- That could be it. - Yeah.
好  我们还有五英里到  今天有比赛
Okay, we're five miles away, and there's a game today.
两小时后开始
It starts in two hours.
好  马上去那里
Okay, go there now.
我通知空中支援
I'll notify aviation.
有情况随时汇报
Keep me posted.
我们马上去  坐稳
We're on our way. Hold on.
空中一号呼叫区域内所有单位
Air One to all units in the zone.
看到目标车辆刚转到莱克街
I have a subject vehicle just turned onto Lake.
他们堵车了  现在沿艾瑞街往西
They're stopped in heavy traffic, heading westbound on Erie,
在休伦街西  往切利街方向
just west of Huron Street, approaching Cherry.
还有一个街区
We're a block out.
我们看到疑犯了
We have eyes on the suspects.
举起手来  举起手来
Let me see your hands! Show me your hands!
-我说什么  -不许动
- What'd I say? - Don't move!
我在跟你说话
I'm talking to you.
把手放在仪表盘上
Put your hands on the dash!
举起手
Put 'em up!
金  你没事吧
Kim, you okay?
没事
I'm good.
下车
Get out.
手放在身后
Hands behind your back.
下车
Get out!
车里的炸弹解除了
The bomb in the van has been disarmed.
移交给联调局前
Just make sure the paperwork's clean
确保处理好所有文书
before you drop it off to the feds.
知道了
Copy that.
你没事吧  金
You okay, Kim?
没事
Okay.
我...
I just--
我真希望我能阻止托马...
I wish I could've stopped Toma from--
我就在那里
I was right there.
你已经尽力了
You did everything you could.
听到了吗
Hear me?
没有他  谁知道会发生什么
Without him, who knows what would've happened.
托马夫人
Mrs. Toma.
介意我进来吗
Do you mind if I come in?
抱歉这么乱
I'm sorry about the mess.
他们刚让我们回来
They just let us back in the house.
抱歉让你们经历这种事
I'm sorry you had to go through this.
他们跟我们说了很难听的话
They called us horrible things.
我们的邻居
Our neighbors.
我们认识他们那么多年了
The people we've known for years.
他们说我儿子是恐怖分子
They called my son a terrorist.
我以为我很了解
I thought I knew Frank...
弗兰克
so well...
托马夫人  听我说
Mrs. Toma, listen,
有件事你们需要知道
here's the thing that you need to know, okay?
不管报纸上怎么说
No matter what the papers say,
不管你们的邻居怎么说
no matter what your neighbors say,
你儿子都是英雄
your son was a hero.
下来  小家伙  不要害怕
Go for it, little man. Don't be scared.
乖孩子
Good boy.
我一直讨厌恶霸
You know, I've always hated bullies.
你来干什么
Hell are you doing here?
他是你的搭档
He was your partner.
你应该保护他
You were supposed to protect him,
不是欺负他  羞辱他
not abuse him and humiliate him.
他没资格做这份工作
He didn't belong on this job.
不  他有资格
No, he belonged.
比你有资格多了
More than you ever will.
是你把那把枪放到他手里  是你扣动了扳机
You put that gun in his hand and you pulled that trigger.
我要你每天晚上
And I want you to think about that
闭上眼睛时都想到这一点
every time you close your eyes at night.
如果不是今天
Oh, if it wasn't today,
那会是下周  或者明年
it'd be next week, or next year.
他肯定会吞枪自尽的
He was always going to eat that gun.
他恨自己
He hated himself.
不  他恨的是你让他有的那种感觉
No, he hated the way that you made him feel.
好吧
Okay.
你该走了
It's time for you to go.
马上
Now.
有一天
One day...
你爸爸不会收拾你的烂摊子了
your dad won't be around to wipe your ass.
等到那一天
And when that day comes,
我会恭候你
I'll be waiting.
-你找我吗  -对  关上门
- You wanted to see me? - Yeah. Shut the door.
我听说你去找罗斯了
I heard you went after Rose.
对  我需要去说出自己的心里话
Yeah. I needed to say my piece.
我明白
Yeah, I get it.
罗斯肯定会得到报应
Look, Rose is going to get what's coming to him.
不过现在
Okay? Just, for now...
我需要你收手
I need you to stay away.
-不  我们需要报告...  -金  我让你收手
- No. We need to file a report- - Kim, I said, stay away.
你对付他的话  你的整个警察生涯就毁了
Listen, you go after him, your entire career goes up in smoke.
明白吗
You understand?
就是这样
It is what it is.
好
Right.
好  有一天他会得到报应  但不是今天
All right, maybe someday, but not today.
好
Right.
进来
Come on in.
丹尼
Denny.
恭喜你破了大案
Well, congratulations on a job well done.
谢谢
Thank you.
但那个孩子
But it was that kid.
托马
Toma.
是他帮我们破了这个案子
He's the one who broke this case wide open.
汉克  我别无选择
Hank, I had no choice.
我必须把他的信息放出去
I had to put that information out there.
我知道
I get it.
现在媒体还在说他是恐怖分子
The press is still out there, calling him a terrorist.
既然我们知道真相了
I mean, now that we know the truth,
我们就得采取措施
we gotta do something about it.
汉克
Hank...
我们想做的事和我们能做的事
There's the realm of what we want to do
是有明确界限的
and the realm of what we can do.
弗兰克·托马要风光下葬
Frank Toma gets a full honors funeral.
这个我们做不到
That is in the realm of what we can't do.
我不满意
That's not good enough.
他有父母
He's got parents.
有家人
A family.
我尽力而为
I'll do what I can.
我很敬佩你  汉克
You know, I admire you, Hank.
你总是知道什么时候战斗  什么时候跑
You always know when to fight and when to run.
可能这就是你生存这么久的原因
Guess that's why you've survived so long.
我从不跑  丹尼
I never run, Denny.
只是等待
I just wait.